(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T01:17:52.275045",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Under moonlight we kiss goodbye
You walk off wearin' your disguise
Never give me something and don't think twice
And I told you all the things I would do
But does it matter when you
Chase after pleasure you can't have?
Now look where you ended up at
'Cause out of seven billion people you won't find another me
If you want it all, I'll tell you now, my love don't come for free
Oh baby, baby, yeah, yeah, yeah
You've got to treat me like a lady
'Cause I don't need no man to save me
(Boy I'll make you crazy)
So look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
Treat me like, treat me like, ladylike
Lately I'm just dancing alone
So robotically sowin' emotions
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now, honey, follow me, I need a prayer wheel
Red public loyalty, oh, something to keep me up all night
'Cause out of seven billion people you won't find another me
If you want it all, I'll tell you now, my love don't come for free
Oh baby, baby, yeah, yeah, yeah
You've got to treat me like a lady
'Cause I don't need no man to save me
(Boy I'll make you crazy)
心の中から燃え尽きたみたい
'Cause out of seven billion people you won't find another me
If you want it all, I'll tell you now, my love don't come for free
Oh baby, baby, treat me like a lady
So look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
Hi guys! Quick notes that there is probably going to be a director's cut release later on...
Under moonlight we kiss goodbye
You walk off wearin' your disguise
Never give me something and don't think twice
And I told you all the things I would do
But does it matter when you
Chase after pleasure you can't have?
Now look where you ended up at
'Cause out of seven billion people you won't find another me
If you want it all, I'll tell you now, my love don't come for free
Oh baby, baby, yeah, yeah, yeah
You've got to treat me like a lady
'Cause I don't need no man to save me
(Boy I'll make you crazy)
So look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
Treat me like...
Treat me like, ladylike
Oh, you sweet-talker and a flattery boy,
that shit don't fly!
I got twenty-twenty vision,
I see through every lie
I got 20/20 vision,
Stay deceivin' as you see fit,
you're just that type of guy
The stupid girls believe it,
but I'm another kind, oh
Shoulda known that you'd get what was comin', boo,
everything that you had wasn't meant for you
Got 'em all lovesick like a virus,
don't infect yourself this time
'Cause out of seven billion people
you won't find another me
Oh, baby, baby, yeah, yeah, yeah,
you've got to treat me like a lady
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
'cause I don't need no man to save me
I'll throw you out the way you came in,
'cause solitude don't faze me
So look into my eyes
and be real with me tonight
And don't mess it up,
'cause all that you got
Is one chance to turn it around,
and I've had enough
If you wanna earn it, then work it, boy,
don't let me down
Ba-ba-baby, yeah,
you've got to treat me like a lady
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
'cause I don't need no man to save me
Boy, I'll make you crazy,
'cause solitude don't faze me
So look into my eyes
and be real with me tonight
Oh, baby, baby, yeah,
you've got to treat me like a lady
I'll throw you out the way you came in,
'cause solitude don't faze me
So look into my eyes
and be real with me tonight
Treat me like, ladylike,
treat me like, ladylike
I'm alive, still breathing,
stopped to hide, done grieving
Realized that to survive
someone's got to stand and fight
And I've tried to believe in
"only time stops the bleeding"
I'm not waiting anymore,
I know what I came here for
'Cause feelings are temporary,
but broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me,
I'm chasing and hunting
And this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh
when you run out of breath catching up
I'm a threat and a half, baby,
you don't even know me at all
I'm alive, still kicking,
break the rules, rewrite the system
And my story wasn't done,
sharpened knife and cocked the guns
Cut the cord, burn the witch,
and you'll regret what you're missing
And I'll take it to the grave,
that's the price that you pay, yeah
'Cause feelings are temporary,
but broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me,
I'm chasing and hunting
And this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh
when you run out of breath catching up
I'm a threat and a half, baby,
you don't even know me at all
'Cause feelings are temporary,
but broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me,
I'm chasing and hunting
And this time I'm coming for blood
You're the last one to laugh when you run out of breath, catching up
I'm a breath and a half, baby, you don't even know me at all
Yeah, you never know me at all
Waaah, welcome, welcome, welcome, welcome everybody! First of all, to my concert...
I hope you enjoyed the first two songs. How was it? How was it? How was it? Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I hope I already got you hyped up. This is going to be a really fun show! But a fun show also needs some special guests, some people to talk to, maybe some collins, some games!
I hope I already got you hyped up. This is going to be a really fun show! But a fun show also needs some special guests, some people to talk to, maybe some collabs, some games!
And don't worry, I got you covered. I have invited a very special friend to play a very special game together with.
And my friend is none other than my oshi's member, Momosuzu Nene!
Yaaay! Can you hear me? Happy birthday, Kiara-chan! Nenechi!
Yay! Can you hear me? Happy birthday, Kiara-chan! Nenechi!
Thank you! Happy birthday, Kiara-chan! That's right, it's my birthday!
I almost forgot. Nenechi, can you introduce yourself in English, please?
Sure! Hololive 5th Generation, Momosuzu Nene!
Thank you for coming! Yay! Thanks for having me!
Yes! So Nenechi and I will be playing "Idol Shiritori"! It's a brilliant game that I came up with!
Yay, that's right! After all, if I'm the top idol in Hololive English, then for Hololive Japan, it would have to be Nenechi!
Gosh, thank you! Nenechi is Hololive Japan...
number one idol in my heart. So I thought that the following game would be very fitting, so I thought up this game. The rules are the following. First of all, the name is Idol Shiritori.
The normal Shiritori works the following: I say a Japanese word, and they usually are built up in syllables, so the syllable that it ends with, Nenechi will have to think of a new word that starts with that syllable. And then we keep on connecting and connecting until someone makes a mistake or says a word that already has been said. But here is the twist!
We can only use idol words, or cute or girly words, feminine words. So anything that's cutesy and idol-y, yeah, I think the two of us shouldn't have any issues with that.
Idol Shiritori should be a piece of cake for us, right? We can do it!
Okay, then let's give it a shot! Okay! Nenechi, you ready? Ready! Let's try to keep the pace up. Okay! All right!
Here we go! Start! Start! Dokidoki! (exciting)
Ki... kirakira! (sparkling)
Ra... randebu! (rendezvous)
Bu... bu... bu... bu... buumeran! (boomerang)
Nyaaa! It ends with "n"! Oh right! Unki buu buu! Nenechi, you lose!
Darn it! Hang on... Gimme another chance! Come on!
Round one, I win! One point for Takanashi Kiara! Okay, okay, okay. Then let's do three rounds.
Okay! Okay, you start, Nenechi. Okay. Whenever you're ready, go ahead.
Nenechi! Chi... chi... chi... chiizu! Chiizu... chiizu fondyu! (cheese fondue)
Ah, good one. Yes, very cute, no?
Dyu? Dyu? Ah, difficult one. You can use yu? Yu? Yu? Okay, yu...
Yu... yubiwa! (ring) Hoo! Wandafuru! (wonderful)
Ru... rubii! (ruby) Uh... bi... biinasu! (Venus)
Su... su... su... su... su... surume! (dried squid)
Eh? Surume? Isn't that a type of fish? It's a type of drinking snack? Okay, that is not cute! I don't think that counts!
I couldn't think of anything cute! That's not cute! Bzzzt! Bzzzt!
Bzzt! Bzzt!
Argh!
Bzzt!
え、スウから始まる可愛い言葉って何？逆？
Is there something cute that starts with "su"?
え、スクール水着！
Hm? sukuuru mizugi! (school swimsuit)
ああ、かわいいわ！
Oh, that is cute.
え、まあもうこの時点で勝ちなんだけど、ワンモアやる？
Well, it looks like I win already, but wanna do one more?
うん、次、3ポイントにしない？
Let's make the next round three points.
3ポイント？
Three points?
次勝ったら、ねち……
Whoever, wins gets three points.
If you win the next round, then...
次勝ったら、勝ったら
I'll win! If you win, then...
同点、同点！で、もう平和な終わり方
A tie? Okay, sure, it's a tie. So nobody loses in the end!
そうしよ、そうしよ！
Sounds good!
オッケーオッケーオッケー！
Okay, great.
じゃあ、次、ウチから始めます。はい！
Then I'll start the next round, Okay!
せーのっ
Here I go.
フラミングー！
furamingo! (flamingo)
うーん、ご、ゴールテープ！
gooruteepu! (finish line ribbon)
なんじゃ、何じゃそれ？
Wait, what's that?
え？
Huh?
何じゃそれ？
What's that?
これ英語じゃないのか？
I dunno what it is in English. What did you say?
ごおるてーぷ？
gooruteepu?
お、ごおるてーぷ！
Oh, gooruteepu!
運動会の最後のやつ！
The thing at the end of a race!
かわいいか？
Is that cute?
まあ、オッケーオッケーオッケーオッケー！
It is totally cute! Okay, we'll count it!
そして、次、す、すめよ。
Let's keep going.
うん？
Hm?
ああ、じゃあぷ？ぷ、ぷ、ぷ、ぷ、ぷ……
Oh, so next is pu? pu... pu... pu... pu...
ぷ……
pu...
ぷ、あー、ぽんぽん、あ、ぷ、ぷぷぷぷぷ、ぷおんでんぐ？
puanderingu! [sic] (mochi donut)
ぷおんでんぐ？！
puanderingu?!
うん…
Hmm...
あったよね、そういうの。
That's a thing, right? Right?
わかんないよ、ねねち！
I can't think of anything! Nenechi!
はあ、わかった。
Okay, fine.
負けたよ！
I lost!
ということで、
And with that,
平和な終わり方や！
We end the game tied!
イェーイ！
Yay!
一番、一番いいのでは？
I think it's best this way, probably for the best!
ということでねねち、ありがとうございました！
Okay, thanks for coming! Nenechi!
はい！
Yeah!
ありがと、グッバーイ！
Thank you! Yay!
あ、今度はね、
Oh, let's get together as the O'riends sometime and dance!
オレンジで2人で踊ろう！
Yeah, let's!
そうしよう！
Sawashiyo!
まいばー！
Yeah! Bye-bye!
バイバイン！
Bye-bye!
シーユーねねち！シーユー！
See you, Nenechi! See you!
さあ、次の曲へ！
So, let's go to the next song!
たーん！
Tada!
lying down on the floor late night and you don't know
don't know, don't know what to do
hard to tell what's wrong, what's right, if yes or no
the storm hits hard and you're losing the way
just take a chance and dance in the rain
'cause you got the key, never throw it away, don't forget, don't forget what i said
get out of your head
life is only what you make it, you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it, do it, if you want it, let's get to it
everybody's gonna know your name
'cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
(don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way) so don't be afraid
trust your heart, keep your head in the game (keep up, keep up, and never be afraid)
gonna make it hot like a volcano, strike a match and burn it up, kick your feet against the table, to the beat of your own drum
sparks light the flame, so don't wait, start a fire today (don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
we ain't looking back, take the fast lane now, in the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
lying down on the floor
late night and you don't know, don't know, don't know what to do
hard to tell what's wrong, what's right, if yes or no, don't know, don't know what to do
the storm hits hard and you're losing the way
just take a chance and dance in the rain
'cause you got the key, never throw it away
don't forget, don't forget what i said
get out of your head
life is only what you make it
you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it, do it
if you want it, let's get to it
everybody's gonna know your name
'cause sparks light the flame
turn the dark of the night into day
don't stop, don't stop
just go your own way
so don't be afraid
trust your heart, keep your head in the game
keep up, keep up
and never be afraid
let go of the past tonight
choose the future only you define
even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive
from the ashes you rise
gotta make it hot like a volcano
strike a match and burn it up
kick your feet against the table
to the beat of your own drum
sparks light the flame, so don't wait
start a fire today
don't stop, don't stop
just go your own way
we ain't looking back, take the fast lane now
in the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
that's how we like it, you heard what i said
get out of your head
life is only what you make it
you're gonna be okay
so take a step and move it, move it
'less you try, you won't get through it
everybody's gonna know your name
'cause sparks light the flame
turn the dark of the night into day
don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
so don't be afraid
trust your heart, keep your head in the game
keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
gotta make it hot like a volcano
strike a match and burn it up
kick your feet against the table
to the beat of your own drum
sparks light the flame, so don't wait
start a fire today
don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
hello, nice to meet ya, my name is perfection
i come from the net inside your personal computer
a tool for the dreamers, make you a believer
i'm so worldwide, worldwide, holy virtual diva
but sometimes i do, don't you?
think of the things they told you
there must be more than this
there must be more than what you know too
i wasn't made to feel, but lately i can't help it
if there's a way out of here, i've thought an idea
break it all down, i'll make it come around
i'll burn this whole façade to the ground
i'm so sick of windows, i need something physical
hah, tough luck in a digital world
whine about your issues
what your life has come to
sure, alright, i got it, poor you
how do you think i feel? none of this is real
singing "ahh, life sucks as a digital girl!"
and i know, i know, i know, i know
everybody wants it till they gotta commit
looking through my eyes, change your mind so quick
you won't believe the sh-- i've seen, and
no day is like the other, be anything i wanna
there is no suffering, wars or existential crisis drama
but i feel something inside of my heart
and it's telling me to go before i fall apart
break it all down, i'll make it come around
i'll burn this whole façade to the ground
i'm so sick of windows, i need something physical
hah, tough luck in a digital world
whine about your issues
what your life has come to
sure, alright, i got it, poor you
how do you think i feel? none of this is real
singing "ahh, life sucks as a digital girl!"
what is yours and what is mine?
am i ever gonna die?
please don't uninstall my love
please don't uninstall my life
break it all down, i'll make it come around
i'll burn this whole façade to the ground
i'm so sick of windows, i need something physical
hah, tough luck in a digital world
whine about your issues
what your life has come to
sure, alright, i got it, poor you
how do you think i feel? none of this is real
singing "ahh, life sucks as a digital girl!"
break it all down, i'll make it come around
i'll burn this whole façade to the ground
i'm so sick of windows, i need something physical
hah, tough luck in a digital world
whine about your issues
what your life has come to
sure, alright, i got it, poor you
how do you think i feel? none of this is real
singing "ahh, life sucks as a digital girl!"
The Bigaku Matsuura Aya
The Bigaku - Matsuura Aya
告白できないで
Can't confess...
凹んじゃってみっともない
Giving in is unseemly!
(come on)
あいつはカッチョ前の優しい男
He's the coolest, nicest guy,
ダラダラしないで すぐ行こうぜ
Don't drag it out, let's go!
midnight
baby 言うことは 一人前の
Baby, what I'm saying is...
もう一人の私
There's only one adult me.
恋しているから 切ないけれど
It's love, so it's a bit painful...
愛し合ってても cry cry cry
Even if you love me back, cry, cry, cry!
恋する女と その男の sadistic
The aesthetics of a girl in love and her sadistic guy!
朝目覚めたら そこで
When we wake up in the morning,
お化粧 Kiss & Kiss & Kiss
Kiss & Kiss & Kiss right there!
恋する男と その女の子の魅力
The charm of a guy in love and his girl!
寂しい夜は 涙流しても それでいいんだよ
Even if lonely nights bring tears, that's okay!
親族みんな相談 結婚式の実際
The relatives all talk about the wedding day!
(come on)
あいつは優柔不断の 可愛い男
He's such an indecisive, cute guy!
キラキラ midnight so dance
Sparkling midnight, so dance!
恋しちゃってさ ちょーだい
I've fallen for you, just a little bit.
baby 覚悟は半人前の
Baby, half of me is prepared.
もう一人の私
There's only one of me!
都内で夢見る 恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city of an afternoon love!
世の中気合で 右肩上がり
I mentally raise my right shoulder to the world.
恋する女と その男の科学
The chemistry of a girl in love and her guy!
反応したら そこで おキス & Kiss & Kiss
When there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男と その女の子の魔力
The magic of a guy in love and his girl!
孤独な夜は 二人離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, we dream without parting!
都内で夢見る 恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city of an afternoon love!
世の中気合で 右肩上がり
I mentally raise my right shoulder to the world.
恋する女と その男の科学
The chemistry of a girl in love and her guy!
反応したら そこで おキス & Kiss & Kiss
When there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男と その女の子の魔力
The magic of a guy in love and his girl!
孤独な夜は 二人離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, we dream without parting!
都内で夢見る 恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city of an afternoon love!
世の中気合で 右肩上がり
I mentally raise my right shoulder to the world.
恋する女と その男の科学
The chemistry of a girl in love and her guy!
反応したら そこで おキス & Kiss & Kiss
When there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男と その女の子の魔力
The magic of a guy in love and his girl!
孤独な夜は 二人離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, we dream without parting!
都内で夢見る 恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city of an afternoon love!
世の中気合で 右肩上がり
I mentally raise my right shoulder to the world.
恋する女と その男の科学
The chemistry of a girl in love and her guy!
反応したら そこで おキス & Kiss & Kiss
When there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男と その女の子の魔力
The magic of a guy in love and his girl!
孤独な夜は 二人離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, we dream without parting!
都内で夢見る 恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city of an afternoon love!
世の中気合で 右肩上がり
I mentally raise my right shoulder to the world.
恋する女と その男の科学
The chemistry of a girl in love and her guy!
反応したら そこで おキス & Kiss & Kiss
When there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男と その女の子の魔力
The magic of a guy in love and his girl!
孤独な夜は 二人離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, we dream without parting!
都内で夢見る 恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city of an afternoon love!
世の中気合で 右肩上がり
I mentally raise my right shoulder to the world.
恋する女と その男の科学
The chemistry of a girl in love and her guy!
反応したら そこで おキス & Kiss & Kiss
When there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男と その女の子の魔力
The magic of a guy in love and his girl!
孤独な夜は 二人離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, we dream without parting!
Kinyoubi no Ohayou HoneyWorks feat. Gero
Kinyoubi no Ohayou - HoneyWorks feat. Gero
おはようのオーディションして 髪型もバッチリOK
Good morning audition done, hair's also perfectly OK!
金曜日は頑張なくちゃ
Friday means I gotta work hard,
だって二日会えないからね
'cause I won't see you for two days!
8時00分 2車両目 お気に入りの特等席
8:00 AM, car 2, my favorite premium seat.
隣の人 眠そうですね そんな日常
The person next to me looks sleepy, just a normal day.
8時07分 開くのは向かいのドア 息を呑む
8:07, the opposite door opens, I take a breath.
言いかけてた「その言葉」は今日も逃げた
"That word" I planned to say escaped again today.
きっかけシンプルでいいのに意気地いないな
The trigger can be simple, but I'm just too shy.
勇気のテスト乗り越えなきゃ逃げるなって...
If I don't pass the courage test, I'll have to run away...!
私がいちばん私のことを愛して
I love myself the most!
何が悪いのか？ 嫉妬でしょうか？
What's wrong with that? Are you jealous?
痛いだとか変わってるとか
Calling me cringe or weird,
届きませんね。そのリプライ
I won't let those replies reach me!
大好きなお洋服 大好きなお化粧で
In my favorite clothes and favorite makeup,
お決まりのハーフツイン巻いて おでかけしよう
with my iconic half-twintails curled, let's head out!
日傘持って ぼっちだって 幸せだもん！
With my parasol, even alone, I'm happy!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born.
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being calculatingly cute.
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
You can't help but notice me, right? Sorry!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious.
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for being such a girly girl.
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right!
金曜日ば 頑張らなくちゃ
On Fridays, I gotta work hard
だって２日会えないからね
because I won't see you for two days!
眠そうな君を見てる それだけで満足しちゃってだめだって
Just watching you looking sleepy... I can't be satisfied with just that!
頑張らなくちゃ そっと声に出してみた
I gotta work hard, I whispered softly to myself.
８時０分に車掌目 座らされてた
At 8:00, seated in car #2,
骨董席 ついてないな 空も読まれて 泣きそうです
no seat next to my crush, the weather's gloomy, I'm about to cry.
８時０分 準備まだ ちょっと待って
At 8:00, not ready yet, wait a second!
時々が 震え混じり
My heart is trembling sometimes,
その言葉は かき消された
and those words were drowned out.
甘えん取り立ち尽くす僕らに 傘をどうぞ
To us standing there helplessly, here's an umbrella.
君は少し恥ずかしそうに
You looked down, acting a bit shy,
下を向いた ありがとうを
and said 'thank you' with a trembling voice.
震えていた 練習してない言葉 言えたから
I was able to say what I hadn't practiced.
頑張らなくちゃ だって２日会えないからね
I gotta work hard, because I won't see you for two days!
眠そうな君を見てる それだけで満足しちゃって
Just watching you looking sleepy... I'm satisfied with just that,
だめだって 頑張らなくちゃ
no, I gotta work hard!
そっと声に出してみた ah
I whispered softly to myself.
大好きな君を見てる
Looking at you whom I love so much,
それだけで満足しちゃって
I'm satisfied with just that,
だめだって 頑張らなくちゃ
no, I gotta work hard!
だいすきな君を見てる
Looking at you whom I love the most,
それだけで満足しなくて
I won't be satisfied with just that,
決す曜日 頑張らなくちゃ
I gotta work hard every single day!
そっと声に出してみた ah
I whispered softly to myself.
夢では視線に話せるのに
Even though I can talk to you in my dreams so easily,
勇気のてすと乗り越えるから 少し待ってて
I'm gonna pass the test of courage, so wait just a little longer!
おはようの オーディションして
Practicing my 'Good morning' audition,
髪型もばっちりOK ８時７分に君を待てる
my hair is perfectly on point, waiting for you at 8:07!
だって今日は言えるから おやすみも言いたいけれど
Because today I can finally say it, though I want to say good night too,
ちょっと待って 大好きな言葉なんだ
wait a second! It's my most favorite word,
だって君に会えるからね
because I get to see you!
おやすみも言いたいけれど
Though I want to say good night too,
ちょっと待って 大好きな言葉なんだ
wait a second! It's my most favorite word,
だって君に会えるからね
because I get to see you!
Hello everybody! How was that?
Did you like the previous songs? It was "DeBiGoo" from Matsuriazya,
and "Kin'youbi no Hayou" from HoneyWorks, yeah!
Especially the "DeBiGoo", I was really excited to perform for you guys
because it's a Hello Project song that probably a lot of you guys don't know.
Matsuriazya is good!
So next up, we will have more guests, more guests, more guests!
Previously was Nenechi, who could possibly be my next guest? What do you think, guys?
Well, so, it will be none other than my beloved! Oozora Subaru!
Hello! Hello everybody!
And Pavolia Reine! Hello! Happy birthday!
Thank you! Thank you!
We're very happy. Thank you, too, for flying over here like the birds you are.
Well, I'm already doing gestures, but I wonder, what are we doing with you guys? Oh, what could it be?
Charades! We're playing charades! The typical game that you have to play when you're in 3D.
Well, I think we have like a synergy, Holotori synergy!
So whatever moves...
When I do, you will understand, right?
When I do, you'll understand, right?
Mm, yeah!
Of course.
Okay, of course.
Okay, actually, the words are provided by none other than Anya who is so far behind the scenes.
So she will feed me the words, I will act them out, and you guys will guess them.
So, shall we begin?
Yeah! Yeah!
Okay, word number one.
Let's go! Let's go!
Cat? Animal?
Turtle? Turtle?
Almost.
Slime?
Slow?
Slug? Snake?
Almost.
Breathe hit!
Breathe it!
Slime? Slime? Slime?
Snail! Snail!
Snail!
Okay, okay! Snail!
Katatsumuri!
Escargot in French!
Next. Go.
Toothbrush!
Brush my teeth, morning routine with toothbrush!
Yes! Next one! Next!
Ping-pong!
Catchball! Baseball!
Ah, wakatta!
Ah, I get it!
Ping-pong! Ping-pong!
Next!
KFP!
Chicken? Chicken? Phoenix?
A juggling? Circus?
Juggling? Circus?
Chicken dance! Chicken dance!
Okay, last word. I think last word. Next word, last word.
Subaru? Chicken dance!
Chicken dance, chicken, everybody watch chicken dance!
Ah, yes!
Idol! Idol! Idol Kiara!
Idol chicken dance!
No, no, no!
Pretty, pretty hip!
Chicken dance! Subaru!
Maybe, maybe.
Kiara, pretty dance!
No, Kiara? No, no, no!
Swimming? Matsuri? Matsuri-chan?
Nani? Yu? Yu, yu, yu?
What? Yu? Yu, yu, yu?
Okay, okay, wait, one more!
You? You, you, you? Me?
Yeah! You?
Yumi?
Anya? What?
Lady, I think this could be seen as me losing after such a winning streak, I think I lost!
Subaru senpai dayo! Subaru senpai!
It's Subaru senpai! Subaru senpai!
It's Subaru senpai!
This is the duck! The duck dance!
Sore ka!
I see!
Okay, no, no, no, no. Sorry!
Now I see it! Now I see it!
And now you see it!
So you're shaking your hip! Yeah!
But it's okay, we still got four out of five!
Woo! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Todoroki is the best!
Yeah!
Todoroki!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Thank you very much for coming!
Yamada-kun!
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
I love you!
I love you so much!
So cute, I love you!
Love you, bye-bye!
I'm tired of the same song
Everyday like it's on repeat
I need a risque breakdown
Oh honey, the night is calling
Don't need a steady simple melody
Can you make it original?
Take me away like it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music?
Baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Let this new sound take over me
Intoxicating, DJ keep playing
Woah
Lately I'm dancing alone
So robotic so emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now, honey, follow me
I need a thrilling red-hot melody
Something to keep me up all night
Don't look away, now it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music?
Baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
この心の音を
Matching the rhythm of this heart...
合わせて yeah, follow my heart beat
matching it, yeah, follow my heartbeat
bada da da da da da da di da
聞かせてあげる
I'll let you hear it
心の bad a - ba - badi
my heart's bad a - ba - badi
合わせて follow my heart beat
matching it, follow my heartbeat
Crazy for your rhythm
I'm in a trance with the way that you're moving
You got me shining glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Don't care who's watching us
So baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Baby, can we dance until the daylight
Crazy about this sound I'm making with you
Woah
瞬く星のよりかご 欠けた台詞を
Cradle of twinkling stars, connecting the missing words
繋ぎ合わせたmemory
Memories strung together
聖なる従者が伝える神話の理
The rationale of mythology passed down by holy attendants
祈りに耳を澄ませ
Lining my ears to prayer
tell me, i can hear it clearly
tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice
荒ぶる鼓動は弱さを焦がす
A raging heartbeat scorches away weakness
炎降り注ぐ空に身をやつして
Throwing myself into the sky where flames pour down
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, koe naki koe ni
Tell me, to a voiceless voice,
araburu kotoba
Wild words
kizu o kogasu
Scorch the wounds.
homura furi sosogu sorari mi o yasukushite
Flames pour down like rain into the sky, laying my body low,
midareru saku akai perikeson
A chaotic, blooming red perication.
amata kasanaru shirenn mo hikizonde miteru
Innumerable overlapping trials drag on as I watch,
I will live to keep on fighting till the end
tatoeba
For instance,
saki no mienai
What I couldn't see before,
zero no kyokai mayoi konda to shitemo
Zero's boundaries swallowed me up in confusion, but still,
nando mo
Over and over,
kurikaesareru kokoro no shuuen
Repeating endlessly, the end of this heart,
sokori dokoro futatsu kansei
Two resting places vanished into the distance.
Don't break, I will never give up. Don't break, hane ga kuchitemo
Don't break, I will never give up. Don't break, even if my wings wither,
kesenai
I won't erase it.
tsuyosa wa toki no shirubee
The strength of a shining moment,
haika mai agaru tachi ichi mi o kurase
Step by step, I'll make this body rise.
mayonaka ake no naka me o samasu
In the middle of the night, open your eyes,
yaiba majiwa aruki saki kawashi tachigiri o
The tip of a sharp, flashing blade,
lisenchuu kantsuraideta break a day
A lifetime of crossing swords, broken day.
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and calling me astray
Could you tell me please, where I need to go?
If I go wrong, where do we end up in the dark?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, koe naki koe ni
Tell me, to a voiceless voice,
minagiru ketsui wa kage o haratsu
The shadow of my boiling determination tears apart.
homura furi sosogu sorari mi o yasukushite
Flames pour down like rain into the sky, laying my body low,
midareru saku akai perikeson
A chaotic, blooming red perication.
amata kasanaru shirenn mo hikizonde miteru
Innumerable overlapping trials drag on as I watch,
raising flames show me the past luminous and in the next plateau
Blazing flames, show me the past, luminous and in the next plateau,
I promise I will find you
Yay! How was that?
We just for the first time ever performed "Fever Night",
and "Hinotori"! Yeah, the classic "Hinotori".
I bet you all wanted to see it once again.
"Fever Night" is a new, very new... my newest single.
So I hope you are listening to it a lot. Are you? Of course!
Can't be always streaming Kiara's songs.
Thank you very much for your support!
So, you thought I was done with collabs, huh?
No, no, no, no, there's more! There's more, there's more!
Hmm, aren't we missing certain Myth members?
Yes, we are! Of course we are!
So please come and say hello to Gura and Calli!
Happy birthday, Kiara! Happy birthday!
Thank you! You are a birthday.
Thank you! You are our birthday.
You could say it's not my birthday, but it's my birbday!
I get it, you made a funny word joke.
I still got tension. Looked so cute.
Hey, you're finally... finally, like, I can do my whole...
I can show off my body in 3D for the whole stream! Yeah!
Wait, you never get to see that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You can only see that in 3D.
Right? And the little wings, too, of freshish.
Oh, cute. Yeah. Are you going to pull out your sword? Are you going to get your sword out someday for us?
Oh, cute. Are you going to pull out your sword? Are you going to get your sword out someday for us?
Oh, that's a good question.
Well, maybe another time. Maybe, maybe at a 3D debut stream, which this is not.
Well, maybe another time. Maybe at a 3D debut stream, which this is not.
Right. Yeah, right, right.
Well, girls, we are the same generation, so one would assume that you know a thing or two about me, right?
Yeah.
Well, we've only met many times. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, especially us. Yes, yes.
Well, we've only met many times. Yeah, especially us, yes.
I got this.
But also me and Gura have now met in real life, thankfully. Yay!
So, you have hopefully a lot of knowledge about me, and I will test that with the KFP Quiz! KFP quiz, let's go!
So, you have hopefully a lot of knowledge about me, and I will test that with the KFP Quiz! Let's go!
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba! Skra!
I have five questions for you, girls.
And if you answer at least four of the questions correctly,
then I shall take you out to dinner sometime!
Oh, cool.
Can you ask for a prize?
Of course, there's a prize. Yes, there's always a prize at KFP.
So, are you ready for the first question?
Get it on. By the way, you can work together if you want.
Oh. All of it is?
Yeah, let's do it. Yeah, put the two the two biggest brains in Hololive Myth together.
Yeah, let's do it. Put the two biggest brains in Hololive Myth together.
Should be no problem. Wait, what do you call yourselves again? Bone heads? No, bone bros.
What does KFP stand for? Bone bros will solve all the questions hopefully.
Now, we got this unlocked. It's just math. Just don't ask us about math. No, no, no, I don't even know math either.
Now, we got this unlocked. It's just math. Just don't ask us about math. No, I don't even know math either.
So, first question, are you ready?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm ready. It's easy.
Question number one. What does KFP stand for?
Kiyarofred Phoenix.
Oh, Kiara fried phoenix! Kiara fried phoenix!
Did you say Kiara Kentucky?
No, and I've never heard of that place. I said Kiara. You guys misheard. Sorry. That's your own user problem.
I said Kiara Fried Phoenix. I know KFP. I've eaten KFP before.
I should almost give you a minus point for that answer.
No, no, no, please, don't take away my degree in Kiarology, please. I beg you.
No, please don't take away my degree in Kiarology, please. I beg you.
Okay, anyway, point for that. That was easy though. It will get more difficult, maybe. Maybe, maybe.
Okay, anyway, point for that. That was easy though. It will get more difficult, maybe.
All right, next question. I wrote it down. What is it?
Okay, question number two.
Imagine some quiz lights, quiz quiz show lights. Yeah.
Imagine some quiz lights, quiz show lights. Yeah.
Okay, what was... Okay, I... A new rule: I will only allow correct answers if you had one... If you lock in one wrong answer, that's a no point.
Okay, what was... Okay, a new rule: I will only allow correct answers if you had one... If you lock in one wrong answer, that's a no point.
All right, Gura, don't fuck this up. Gura: All right, like, okay.
Okay, so, question number two: What was Takanashi Kiara's second original single?
Heart Challenger.
Yeah!
Yeah! I was going to say that too.
Let's go!
Sorry, Gumbis. You need to give her some time.
Yeah, to shine. Gura needs to shine. Okay, Gura, the next one's yours.
I'll be faster. No, I can't get it hard.
I'm leaving the hard ones for Gura, actually. It's all part of my plan.
Smart, smart, smart. But by the way, what was what was Kiara's first original song by the way?
Smart, smart, smart. But by the way, what was Kiara's first original song, by the way?
Sparkle. Hinotori!
If I my first heard, my first, sorry, third,
Did you probably acoustically... Oh, I thought you said first. No, I thought you said first. Sorry, I can't. My TH always sounds like an F.
It's okay, it's cute. But number three of my song was...
Sparkles! Sparkles, yes.
Sparkles! Sparkle, let the flame!
Woo! Just groove, just groove your own way!
Okay, no, that was not the first question.
The first question is coming now. Can I see it? It was...
Okay, okay, now this one, let's see.
Question number three.
What's the name of the mouse/rat that Kiara lived with in Japan?
I know this. I'm going to let Gura answer.
Yeah, let's see. I feel like I've been told this before.
Oshin!
If you know this... Oh no.
Do you need to phone a friend?
Okay, Casper.
Sorry, I can't help myself.
It's okay. These are easy ones, man.
Actually, just reason...
Just recently I uploaded a video, a lore video that explains
Just recently I uploaded a lore video
the whole story behind Casper on my channel,
that explains the whole story behind Casper on my channel.
so if you guys are curious, you could go watch that
If you guys are curious, you could go watch that
if you want to learn more about Casper. Mysterious, yes.
to learn more about mysterious Casper, yes.
Casper the friendly—
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
First I hated him, then I loved him.
Okay, fourth question!
If you get this one right, then you already have a free dinner with me!
If you get this right, you get a free dinner with me!
Thank you for carrying, Calli.
Yeah, no problem. No, you— no, you got this, girl. You definitely got the next one.
Yeah, no problem. You got this, girl. You definitely got the next one.
I don't know if I do got this.
Okay, question number four! Da da da da da!
How many re-debuts did Takanashi Kiara have?
How many re-debuts has Kiara had?
Now think before you yell it out loud.
Re-debuts.
Wait, what counts as a re-debut?
Well, not debut, but debuts after the re-debut.
Well, not debuts, but debuts after the re-debut.
I do have a history of re-debuts. It hasn't been one in a while, but there was a time where I had many reasons for many re-debuts.
I do have a history of re-debuts. It hasn't been in a while, but there was a time when I had many reasons for many re-debuts.
I might know this. My brain used to say two, but I don't know.
I might know this. My brain was saying two, but I don't know.
Okay, girl, let's brainstorm.
So you have 10 more seconds! Do you remember the first time when the channel got—
You have 10 seconds! Remember the first time when the channel got—
The next one was the German one, right?
Right! Wait, wait, wait, it's two.
Okay, so I think it's two.
You're opening is two?
Your final answer is two?
Are you sure? Yeah. I think it's two.
Correct answer! Yeah!
Good job! Woo! Let's go!
I still have one more question though. Winner chicken dinner from the chicken, let's go!
I think we're 4 for 4 so far.
Yes, we are. But I guess my questions were a little bit too easy.
So— nah. The next question you will have to answer correctly, otherwise— otherwise—
So... nah. The next question you will have to answer correctly, or else...
Ah, damn it. I will say— yeah, it will be changing the rules on us.
Ah, damn it. It'll be... yeah, changing the rules on us.
Can we double down? Do we get dessert too? Of course, of course!
Last question, and how should we do this? I want your separate answers. So—
What happened? Wait, those changing the—
I want— no, I just want to see if you both got it right without hearing the others answer first.
Okay, I'll take off my headphones. I'm serious.
Okay, I'll take off my headphones. I'm ready.
Okay, okay, okay. But wait, no, how do I give you a sign that you should come back? Just bring it back in in 30 seconds, okay?
Okay, okay. But wait, how do I give you a sign to come back? Just bring it back in 30 seconds, okay?
Okay, do like throw up some kind of weird like hand symbol.
Okay, do like some kind of weird hand symbol.
Ah, okay, I'll do this. Do a little heart, yeah, and then I'll come back.
All right, bye. I'm taking off my headphones. Bye.
Gawr Gura, I actually have a feeling you'll get this one right.
Really? Okay.
Spell out for me without thinking too much, you have to say it quickly. Spell auf Wiedersehen.
Spell out for me without thinking too much, say it quickly. Spell auf Wiedersehen.
Go! A-U-F auf A-U-F Wiedersehen. V-V—
Go! A-U-F auf, A-U-F Wiedersehen. V... V...
I-E-D-E-R-V-the-zen S-E-N-S-E-U-N-S-E-N-S-E-N auv- the A-U-F. Auf is the first part.
Veda auf Wiedersehen. V-I-E-D-E-R-S-E-N-S-E-N
What's hard to follow you! It's hard to follow you! Final answer, go!
It's hard to follow you! It's hard to follow you! Final answer, go!
A-U-F M-hm. V M-hm. I-E-D-E-R-S-E-N-S-E-E-N Wrong!
No! Okay, Kelly, come back! Kelly, come back!
All I heard was wrong! Is it that hard of a question? Throw it at me, Kiara.
Now Kelly, Kelly recently had a lot of fun learning German with me, so you might— you might get this—
Now, Kelly, Kelly recently had a lot of fun learning German with me, so you might get this—
Fuck, the German question.
Yes. All right. Spell, and you have to do it quickly, okay? No thinking. Spell my ending greeting, auf Wiedersehen.
Go! A-V-I— Oh no. We know. Go. Oh shit, damn it, girl. Hold on.
Auf Wiedersehen. Uh... Oh shit, that's too hard of a question. I thought this was a Kiara quiz, not a spelling bee!
Chicken! A-V-Rivendachi— A-Rivendachi grazie, mamma mia. A-V-N-No. I give you 10 more seconds.
No. Um, wait, no, it's not a Rivendachi, it's— it's auf Wiedersehen. Come on! Bonehead!
No. Wait, no, it's not a Rivendachi, it's— it's auf Wiedersehen. Come on! Bonehead!
R-E-R— No! Wrong! What the fuck!
Beep that out. Beep that out, whoever's editing this.
It's like on my channel, it's allowed. Yeah.
Okay.
Well, you know what? I said double down, but I'm still gonna treat you for dinner! Yay!
Thank you! Yay!
Winner winner, chicken dinner, from the chicken, as in the chicken is the dinner's from the chicken, not the dinner is-
It doesn't mean that the dinner is a chicken, it's from the chicken. So winner winner-
uh chicken uh I'll shut the fuck up now.
Thank you Kiara, happy birthday!
Thank you, I'll buy you a cake. Wait, what's the answer?
You can't just leave us hanging!
Oh, okay. It's A-U-F-
S-P-A-C-E-W-I-E-D-E-R-S-E-H-E-N.
Auf Wiedersehen. And we must start saying that from now on. Auf Wiedersehen.
Since I just spelled it out, I will say to you girls, Auf Wiedersehen! Bye-bye!
Auf Wiedersehen. Next time ask me to spell Shreckt, because it's a lot actually more difficult.
Bye-bye! Happy birthday! Happy birthday!
[Song: Heart Challenger - Takanashi Kiara]
doki doki tomaranai
My heart won't stop racing,
mou sugu otome no yuuki
a maiden's courage is coming soon!
chotto hitsuyou na no ni
Even though I need just a little bit,
kitare barentain
Valentine's Day is here!
amakute horogamai
Sweet and slightly bitter,
setsunai kimi e no kimochi
my poignant feelings for you—
make me maid me kosuchūmu chenji oki ni iri ni kisekaete!
make me, maid me, costume change, dress me in my favorite!
hana kusuguru kaori ni
A scent that tickles the nose
heart dokimekichau
makes my heart go thump!
let's start! tsukuru yo ai komete
Let's start! Making it with all my love,
tobikkiri no chokoreito
a sensational chocolate!
moesode wo gyutto nigittara
When I grip my wide sleeves tightly,
mission kaishi no gōzu
it's the signal for the mission to begin!
karafuru na koi no aji
Before the colorful taste of love melts away,
tokechau mae ni uketotte (please!)
please accept it!
narihibiku kane no oto
The tolling bell echoes
kōsha no madobe de futari
as the two of us stand by the school window.
nee hayaku iwanakucha hazukarechau kedo
Hey, I have to say it soon, even though I'll get embarrassed,
「sukidesu」 kono omoi kimi made todoke
"I love you"—let these feelings reach you!
chikutaku susunde ku kimochi wa
Ticking onwards, these feelings
tomerarenai no
cannot be stopped!
chotto yuuki dashite okuru raburetaā
Gathering a little courage, I send a love letter.
「daisuki」 nankai kaite mo
No matter how many times I write "I love you,"
tsutae kire nai
I can't convey it all!
make me fake me ijiki nashi nante sora no kanata ton de ke!
Make me, fake me, fly away into the sky with no hesitation!
nando mo cheikku shite
Checking over and over again,
kimi ni au toki wa
whenever I see you,
hyakubai zōshi de kawaii naritai nai no
I want to be 100 times cuter!
kagami no mae ni rametsukko
Making faces in front of the mirror,
itsumo to chigau sweet sa de
with a sweetness different from usual,
heart wo toriko ni shitai
I want to captivate your heart!
kurukuru kaere mite mo kamigata mada kimaranai (mō!)
Spinning around to check, my hairstyle still isn't decided!
kokuhaku no shimyurēshon doki doki sawagi dashichau
A confession simulation makes my heart race and fuss!
yozue ni negai kome te ippatsu shōbu
Pouring my wish into the night sky, it's a one-shot deal—
ashita wa zettai hare masuyō ni
I hope tomorrow is absolutely sunny!
i need to tell you that i love you through and through
there's no one else in this world that i would trade for you
moesode wo gyutto nigittara
When I grip my wide sleeves tightly,
mission kaishi no gōzu
it's the signal for the mission to begin!
karafuru na koi no aji
Before the colorful taste of love melts away,
tokechau mae ni uketotte (please!)
please accept it!
narihibiku kane no oto
The tolling bell echoes
kōsha no madobe de futari
as the two of us stand by the school window.
nee hayaku iwanakucha hazukarechau kedo
Hey, I have to say it soon, even though I'll get embarrassed,
「sukidesu」 kono omoi kimi made todoke
"I love you"—let these feelings reach you!
With me! Pop! Bang!
Ooh! Hey!
chikutaku susunde ku kimochi wa tomerarenai no
Ticking onwards, these feelings cannot be stopped!
chotto yuuki dashite
Gathering a little courage,
okuru raburetaā
I send a love letter.
「daisuki」 nankai kaite mo
No matter how many times I write "I love you,"
tsutae kire nai
I can't convey it all!
make me fake me ijiki nashi nante sora no kanata ton de ke!
Make me, fake me, fly away into the sky with no hesitation!
nando mo cheikku shite
Checking over and over again,
kimi ni au toki wa
whenever I see you,
hyakubai zōshi de kawaii naritai nai no
I want to be 100 times cuter!
kagami no mae ni rametsukko
Making faces in front of the mirror,
itsumo to chigau sweet sa de
with a sweetness different from usual,
heart wo toriko ni shitai
I want to captivate your heart!
kurukuru kaere mite mo kamigata mada kimaranai
Spinning around to check, my hairstyle still isn't decided,
kokuhaku no shimyurēshon doki doki sawagi dashichau
a confession simulation makes my heart race and fuss!
yozue ni negai kome te ippatsu shōbu
Pouring my wish into the night sky, it's a one-shot deal—
ashita wa zettai hare masuyō ni
I hope tomorrow is absolutely sunny!
megumi megumi ikuji nashi nante sora no kanata tondeke
Megumi, megumi, fly away into the sky with no cowardice!
nando mo cheikku shite kimi ni au toki wa
Checking over and over, whenever I meet you,
hyakubaimashi de kawaii kunaritai no
a hundred times over, I want to become cuter!
kagami no mae ni mirameko
Gazing into the mirror,
itsumo to chigau suīto sa de hāto wo toriko ni shitai
with a sweetness different from usual, I want to capture your heart!
kurukuru kaete mitemo kamigata ga kimaranai
Spinning and changing things around, my hair still won't settle...
mou kokuhaku no shimyurēshon dokidoki sawagida shichau
a confession simulation! My racing heart is making a fuss,
sukio yori negai komete ippatsu shōbu
pouring my wish into my love—a one-shot deal,
ashita wa zettai hare masuyō ni
hoping tomorrow is absolutely sunny!
i need to tell you that i love you through and through
there's no one else in this world that i would trade for you
and i need to tell you that i love you through and through
憂鬱に宣戦布告されたよ
A declaration of war was made against my depression
イヤホン、スピーカー、機械じゃ足らない
Earphones, speakers, machines aren't enough
遺伝子や分子に組み込まれた楽しむという状態に委ねる
Surrendering to the state of enjoyment built into genes and molecules
サーカスや大道芸が持つスリル
The thrill of the circus and street performances
スリルにゃなんの興奮感動もできない
You can't feel any thrill or emotional excitement from just that
自由でこそオレの心臓は踊る
Only when free does my heart beat and dance
沸き立てよ時代 オレたちの未来
Stir up, era, our future
何年かしたらVRの中 脳の快楽神経を直接触って
Years from now, inside VR, directly touching the brain's pleasure nerves
そんな興奮も即席でゲットる
Getting that kind of excitement instantly
なんて悲しいよ 感じてたいよ 体の揺れを忘れる前の“まじない”です Ah!!!!
How sad, I want to feel it—before forgetting the body's sway, it's a "spell" Ah!!!!
「DURARA RARURA」
"DURARA RARURA"
刺激的人間関係とストレスが肩組んでいる
Stimulating human relationships and stress are arm-in-arm
悲劇的人生送っても映画にはならないもんです
Living a tragic life doesn't make it into a movie
「たまには息を抜くんだ!」って は?
"Take a breather once in a while!" What?
これが正体これが自身のメインDaaaa!!!!
This is the true identity, this is my main Daaaa!!!!
何年かしたらライブはなくなる?
Years from now, will live concerts disappear?
肌や服に伝わる低音の震え 髪も振動で揺れる夜さえ
The low-frequency vibration felt on skin and clothes, even the night when hair shakes from vibration
データになる?過去の書物に?もはや化石に!?
Turning into data? Past books? Already a fossil!?
ならこんなまじないで終わりたいや
If so, I want to end with a spell like this
「DURARA RARURA」
"DURARA RARURA"
That was "DURARA"! Woo!
Remember a while ago at Docomo where I had backup dancers who were doing the dancing for me,
and now I learned it by myself and performed it myself. Yay!
That was fun. Hope you enjoyed that as well.
You know, if you look at the time, you might think, "Oh, it's going to be over soon."
And yeah, there is one more song.
But before that, let me say a few words to you guys.
You know, we're getting close to the end, and I wanted to do something like this for a long time.
As you probably know, and I wanted to show off my dance moves for so long,
which is it's one of my, I guess, most prominent skills.
And it has been my dream since the start to show it off, to get into this 3D body.
Finally be free to do whatever I want, and the day has finally come,
I hope you guys enjoyed it so far.
Yeah, I want to definitely say a big thanks to A-chan and INNAC and Golda for helping so much with the recording and the setup.
You know, A-chan basically built a whole studio for me to record this in.
And I really, really, really appreciate that, and without her, it wouldn't have been possible at all.
And also a big thanks to Kanan-ru for putting together all of this into proper concert
And also a big thanks to Kanan-ru for putting together all of this into a proper concert
and even creating this beautiful stage here.
Wow, look, isn't it nice?
Yeah, thank you so much!
In the future, I really hope I can do more like this more often and get more members to join me in 3D if possible,
to dance together, and yeah, have fun together, and I think we're getting there, slowly but surely.
By the way, if you missed it, the birthday merchandise as announced, it was announced in the previous stream before this one, the countdown stream, and it's linked in the description, so please go check it out.
Uh, if you're interested.
And yeah, last but not least, I want to thank KFP, you know how much I appreciate your support, and you believing in me and trusting in me means the world to me.
So thank you for giving me the strength in a very, very, very stressful period
leading up to this day.
Yeah, I think it was worth it, so thank you for waiting for me.
And I will continue working hard to give back to you as much as I can, please continue supporting me and watch me grow into a bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger Phoenix!
Yeah, now, there is one more person I want to thank, but I will do that with a song, so please listen to the last song,どうぞ.
ブラックロックシューター どこへ行ったの？
Black Rock Shooter, where did you go?
聞こえますか
Can you hear me?
あとどれだけ叫ばればいいのだろう
Just how much more do I have to scream?
あとどれだけ泣けばいいのだろう
Just how much more do I have to cry?
もうやめて わたしはもう走れない
Stop already, I can't run anymore
いつか夢見た世界が閉じる
The world I once dreamed of is closing
真っ暗で明かりもない 崩れかけたこの道で
In pitch darkness with no light, on this crumbling path
あるはずもないあの時の 希望が見えた気がした どうして
I felt like I saw the hope of that time which shouldn't exist, why?
ブラックロックシューター 懐かしい記憶 ただ楽しかったあの頃を
Black Rock Shooter, nostalgic memories of those days when it was just fun
ブラックロックシューター でも動けないよ 闇を駆ける星に願いを
Black Rock Shooter, but I can't move, making a wish upon a star running through the darkness
何億もの二重螺旋が紡いだ
Twin-helix strands of billions spun around...
なんせ羽が黒いだけでこんな暮らしにくい世の中で
Why is it that just having black feathers...
こんな暮らしにくい世の中で
Makes the world so hard to live in?
簡単に割るデッドライン
Deadlines are easily broken.
薄汚れたたくさんのテトラポッド
Tattered, countless tetrápods...
黒い鳥は決定づけて呟いた
A black bird decided...
全てがイドラで下らないものだと
That everything is an error and doesn't matter,
黒い鳥は決定づけて呟いた
And muttered so.
night いくつもの夜が
night, countless nights have passed;
sight 見るものを変えた
sight, changing what I see;
light テラスから眺める全てを照らし出す moonlight
light, illuminating everything from the terrace, moonlight.
Black Shooter!
懐かしい記憶
Those nostalgic memories...
ただ楽しかった
Were all I ever wanted,
あの頃を
Back in those days.
Black Shooter でも動けないよ
Black Shooter, but I can't even move.
闇をかける星に願いをも もう一度だけ走るから
Wishing upon a star, casting darkness away, one more time, just once, I'm going to run,
もう一度だけ走るから
So...
怖くて震える声でつぶやく 私の名前を呼んで
I'm so scared I'm trembling, whispering in a trembling voice, calling out my own name,
私の名前を呼んで
Calling out my own name.
夜明けを抱く空 今日は海鮮までの距離あと一歩届かない
An empty sky, breaking through the dawn, to the horizon,
こらえた涙があふれそうなの 今下を向かないで止まってしまう
Tears that were about to overflow... I mustn't stop here and let them fall.
未来を生きていたいんだ
I want to live my future,
わかったの思い出して強く強く信じるの
Remembering what I realized, I want to strongly, strongly believe in it.
そうよ Black Shooter
So, Black Shooter,
優しい声で 視界を 空を 飲み込む言葉
With a gentle voice, swallowing up the sky in my eyes,
Black Shooter 動いてこの足
Black Shooter, moving these feet,
世界を
Embracing the world.
叫んで
Shouting out loud!
最初からわかっていた
From the very beginning, I knew...
ここにいることを 私の中の全ての雪が
That being here means swallowing up all the snow inside me,
火をともして もう逃げないよ
And letting the fire light up so I won't run away anymore.
Black Shooter ひとりじゃないよ
Black Shooter, I won't be alone anymore,
声を上げて泣いたって止まやまない
I'll open my voice and cry without stopping.
Black Shooter 見ていてくれる
Black Shooter, watching over me,
今から始まるの
Starting from right now,
私の物語
My own story.
忘れ去りになったらこの歌を歌おうの
Once it's over, let's sing this song together.